<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fab Five</string>


    <string name="text_view">Jahangirnagar University</string>
    <string name="text_view_age">PMIT-IIT</string>
    <string name="scroll_view">

        MESSAGE FROM DIRECTOR: It is a great pleasure and honor for me to serve as the Director of the Institute of Information Technology
        at Jahangirnagar University (IIT-JU). The Institute began in 1987 with the mission of training individuals in computer-related skills.
        It launched a bachelor\'s degree program in information technology in 2009 with the clear goal of meeting the cutting-edge demands of
        the information technology industry. The Institute is committed to cultivating an environment that fosters innovation, creativity, and
        excellence in its students. At IIT, we are strong advocates of interdisciplinary research and development that benefits both industry and society.

        VISION: The vision of the IIT-JU is to enlighten the students through need-based academic innovation
        and research works and prepare them for the real-life challenges in the field of ICT.

        MISSION: The mission of IIT-JU is to create splendid students by enhancing knowledge and competitiveness
        through excellent education, hands-on experience, state-of-the-art research, and industry collaboration.

    </string>
    <string name="edit_text">Type here :</string>
    <string name="write_edit_text">Type anything</string>
    <string name="button_listener">Listener</string>


    <string name="button_in_grid">Next Page</string>
    <string name="col1">Name</string>
    <string name="col2">ID</string>
    <string name="row1Name">Ashik-E-Elahi</string>
    <string name="row1Roll">223124</string>
    <string name="row2Name">Jannatul Joinal Ananna</string>
    <string name="row2Roll">223139</string>
    <string name="row3Name">Md. Alamgir Hossain</string>
    <string name="row3Roll">223134</string>
    <string name="row4Name">Md. Masfiqur Rahman</string>
    <string name="row4Roll">223143</string>
    <string name="row5Name">Rahul Sarker</string>
    <string name="row5Roll">223111</string>
    <string name="table_button">Next</string>
    <string name="table_button_back">Back</string>

    <string name="ani_button_blink">Blink</string>
    <string name="ani_button_Rotation">Rotation</string>
    <string name="ani_button_fade">Fade</string>
    <string name="ani_button_move">Move</string>
    <string name="ani_button_slide">Slide</string>
    <string name="ani_button_zoom">Zoom</string>
    <string name="ani_button_stop_animation">Stop Anim</string>


</resources>